[{"answer": " It's the biggest on earth!  I swear!  It's a 5", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Taller?  What", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Eight years ago.  In that whole time, I never left my computer", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Good and bad.  They think that's what caused this.  Me eye tumor. Microwaves from the screen.  It's the size of a grapefruit.  Heavy too", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "It can with my new computer code, you and me, we can do it together", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "That's why you're so perfect.  You have something I don't have", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Listen, my friend, it's been a rough day.  I'll call you about his next week", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": " I'm already dead", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Why", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Dark", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "If anyone asks about my frien", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Exactly.  Don't you wonder where I'm really hiding my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "No need.  She does all her own stunts", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": " Even the fall from the plane", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Why not", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "an emotional wall, I know. That's wh", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Of course", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "... so much like her", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What?... What did you say", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "What I do to my friend", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I got them to remove the reflection.  The mirror's metaphor to show how her character's inwardly dead", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Who else?  It's always my friend's idea", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "my friend!  my friend!  Can we have a minute?  What brings you here tonight", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "There's a rumor that you're more than just", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Is she here", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " Somebody said she was here", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yes oh my, God.  Is that you, my friend?!  I've been wanting to talk to you", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "I can't imagine how you ever let a man like that go.  I owe Viktor everything", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I want to reassure you, my friend, there's absolutely nothing going on between my friend and I", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "I'm going to tell you a secret now, my friend.  my friend is not a real person.  I invented her", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " No, no, I didn't trip over her. You don't understan", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "We don't believe daddy because we don't want to believe we were taken in too", "docId": "Simone_Andrew_Niccol.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "Listen to what you're saying, mom. Is there any evidence she is", "qsentId": 34}]